{"questions":[{"question":"Which of the following is not an agile best practice","level":1,"answers":["Delivering working software frequently.","Performing unit testing as part of the development process.","Dividing the development process into a series of short iterations, where each iteration focuses on a specific set of features or requirements.","Lack of collaboration with the customer"],"team":"Spider","correctAnswer":4},{"question":"Which of the following is not supposed to be discussed during the daily stand-up meetings (daily scrum meetings):","level":2,"answers":["Tasks to be done for the day","Current obstacles","Planning for the iteration","Recently completed tasks"],"team":"Spider","correctAnswer":3},{"question":"Which of the following distinguishes Scrum from Agile","level":3,"answers":["Emphasize the importance of delivering working software to the customer regularly.","A set of predetermined roles","Placing strong emphasis on continuous improvement using feedback mechanisms.","Involving the customer in the development process"],"team":"Spider","correctAnswer":2},{"question":"How to ensure that the most prominent features are delivered first","level":3,"answers":["Using a requirements traceability matrix to track requirements through the development process.","Prioritizing based on personal preferences","Decreasing the priority of non-functional requirements","Not considering feasibility of implementation"],"team":"Spider","correctAnswer":1},{"question":"Which of the following must be avoided when specifying software requirements","level":1,"answers":["Tracking changes to requirements","Involving all stakeholders","Not gathering enough details","Prioritizing requirements"],"team":"Spider","correctAnswer":3},{"question":"Which of the following is not a benefit to conducting code review:","level":2,"answers":["Detecting early defects and mistakes in code","Providing an opportunity for team members to share knowledge","Improving code quality, ensuring that the code follows best practice and conventional standards","Requiring additional time and resources to review code"],"team":"Spider","correctAnswer":4},{"question":"Which of the following fulfills the goal of code review","level":2,"answers":["Rewriting code","Encouraging collaboration and communication between development team members","Replacing unit testing","Enforce coding style on other team members"],"team":"Spider","correctAnswer":2},{"question":"Which of the following does not demonstrate how MVC components interact with each other:","level":1,"answers":["The controller stores data","The controller processes user requests from View and communicates with the Model to handle the requests","The view may send input from user to the controller, and it sends the data to model to handle them.","The user interacts with the View, which sends a request to the Controller"],"team":"Spider","correctAnswer":1},{"question":"Which of the following is not a benefit of layered architecture:","level":1,"answers":["It is easier to add new features or make changes, as the different layers can be adjusted independently","Improves reusability","Increased complexity","Layers can be tested independently, making it easier to test"],"team":"Spider","correctAnswer":3},{"question":"Which of the following design patterns is not a behavioral design pattern:","level":2,"answers":["Chain of responsibility","Fa√ßade","Observer","Template"],"team":"Spider","correctAnswer":2},{"question":"Which principle of the Norman\u2019s design principles stated below does not match with its definition:","level":3,"answers":["Visibility: Make essential elements visible so that users can easily find them.","Consistency: reduce confusion and increase usability.","Constraints: to guide users towards appropriate actions.","Mapping: to indicate the actions that can be performed with an object."],"team":"Spider","correctAnswer":4},{"question":"Which of the following is not a characteristic of white box testing:","level":3,"answers":["Has access to the outputs of the system","Can be used in various stages of the software development","Has full access to the internal structure of the system","Focuses on the internal logic"],"team":"Spider","correctAnswer":1},{"question":"Which of the following annotations is not part of the JUnit testing framework:","level":3,"answers":["@Deprecated","@SuppressWarnings","@Ignore","@After"],"team":"Spider","correctAnswer":2},{"question":"Which of the following is not a benefit of TDD (Test Driven Design):","level":1,"answers":["Reduce Time spent on debugging","Thinking carefully about the code and how it should be structured leads to better code design","Identify bugs early in the development process","Lack of flexibility and hard to make changes"],"team":"Spider","correctAnswer":4},{"question":"Which of the following skills is not a required skill for corrective maintenance:","level":2,"answers":["Project management","Attention to detail","Communication skills","Troubleshooting"],"team":"Spider","correctAnswer":1},{"question":"Which of the following is not a characteristic of adaptive maintenance","level":3,"answers":["Performed in response to changes in the operating conditions of a system","May involve significant changes to the system","Performed in response to a problem or malfunction that has been identified in a system","Focused on the future needs and capabilities of the system"],"team":"Spider","correctAnswer":3}]}